Guide to the Don Gale KSL editorial video collection 1938-2010 1978-1997
Multimedia Archives, J. Willard Marriott Library, University of Utah
Don Gale KSL editorial video collection
1938-2010
1978-1997
University of Utah Libraries, Special Collections Audio Visual Archives Special Collections 295 South 1500 East Salt Lake City, Utah 84112-0860 801-581-8864 http://www.lib.utah.edu/collections/multimedia-archives/
A1055
Gale, Don, 1933-
125 U-matic videocassettes, 59 Betacam videocassettes, 6 VHS videocassettes, 115 DVDs.
The Don Gale KSL editorial video collection (1938-2010, bulk 1978-1997) consists of the complete 19-year series of daily editorials delivered by Gale at the end of the evening news on Salt Lake City television station KSL. The collection touches on myriad local and national issues affecting Utahns and highlights the state's social, political, environmental and cultural history during the latter half of the 20th century. The collection also contains various tributes to local businessman and philanthropist "Izzi" Wagner. Gale began writing editorials in 1977, went on the air in 1978, and continued broadcasting until his retirement in 1998.
Biographical Note
G. Donald Gale wrote, produced and broadcast daily editorial segments for KSL News in Salt Lake City, Utah from 1977 until his retirement in 1998. Former Vice President for News and Public Affairs at Bonneville International Corporation, Gale earned Bachelor of Arts (B.A.), Master of Arts (M.A.) and Doctor of Philosophy (Ph.D.) degrees from the University of Utah and served on the faculty there and at Weber State University. He is the author of the book Bags to Riches about Utah businessman and philanthropist "Izzi" Wagner. Don Gale continues to write a monthly column for the Deseret Morning News and the Ogden Standard-Examiner. He is President of Words, Words, Words, Inc., a communication consulting company.
The Don Gale KSL editorial video collection (1938-2010) consists of the complete 19-year series of daily editorials delivered by Gale at the end of the evening news on Salt Lake City television station KSL. The collection touches on myriad local and national issues affecting Utahns and highlights the state's social, political, environmental and cultural history during the latter half of the 20th century. The collection also contains various tributes to local businessman and philanthropist "Izzi" Wagner.
All of Gale's original editorials have been digitized and are available for viewing on the DVDs detailed in this finding aid. A history and list of the editorials may also be found in Gale's book KSL Editorials 1978-1997: A Personal History, which is available with the paper collection registers in the Special Collections Reading Room. Izzi Wagner materials are available on the DVDs listed at the end of the collection.
The materials are arranged chronologically. KSL editorials are listed first, followed by materials about Izzi Wagner.
Materials must be used on-site; no use of original material, access copies will be made available for viewing. Five business days advanced notice required. Access to parts of this collection may be restricted under provisions of state or federal law, condition of the material, or by donor.
Donated by Don Gale in 2010 and 2012.
See also the Don Gale papers (Accn 2584).
Wagner, Izzi, 1915-2005; KSL (Television station: Salt Lake City, Utah); Utah; Editorial; Television news; Media and Communication; Moving Images; Moving images
- KSL editorials, 1978-1998; 2010
  - KSL editorials, 1977 December-1978 August; DVD (Disc 1)
    Editorials before August 15 were written by Don Gale and delivered by L.H. Curtis. Beginning on August 15, 1978, editorials were written and broadcast by Don Gale. Although editorials were not routinely recorded for archvie during this period, the following editorials were preserved.
    - Carter and the Central Utah Project (CUP), 1978 February 02 (Video 1)
    - City franchise tax (Commissionaire's Disease), 1977 December 04 (Video 2)
    - Super Bowl (Orange Crush), 1978 January 14 (Video 3)
    - Story time for the Department of Energy (story book), 1978 February 01 (Video 4)
    - State and local taxes (graphic of tax load), 1978 February 21 (Video 5)
    - Choose the news (Panama Canal debate), 1978 February 23 (Video 6)
    - National procrastination week (typewriter/cartoon), 1978 March 11 (Video 7)
    - Federal aid to education, 1978 March 18 (Video 8)
    - Utah's teacher shortage (class size limits), 1978 March 19 (Video 9)
    - Money may be hazardous to your health, 1978 March 22 (Video 10)
    - Vandalism in Granger, 1978 March 23 (Video 11)
    - The role of the media (information vs. knowledge), 1978 March 25 (Video 12)
    - Concrete fender benders (Main Street beautification), 1978 March 27 (Video 13)
    - Moratorium on annexation, 1978 March 28 (Video 14)
    - City commission pay increase (drop in bucket), 1978 April 19 (Video 15)
    - Editorial quote from Sam Brown, 1978 April 26 (Video 16)
    - Citizen involvement (Glen Miller), 1978 April 28 (Video 17)
    - Noise pollution (blender), 1978 May 6 (Video 18)
    - Earthquake protection (Veterans Hospital), 1978 May 13 (Video 19)
    - Drunk driving and the law, 1978 May 14 (Video 20)
    - American education (student editorial), 1978 May 15 (Video 21)
    - "O! Calcutta" (snake oil cartoon), 1978 May 19 (Video 22)
    - Reverse discrimination (Nathaniel Colley quote), 1978 May 31 (Video 23)
    - School is out (graduation), 1978 June 1 (Video 24)
    - Freedom of the press day, part 1, 1978 June 6 (Video 25)
    - Freedom of the press day, part 2, 1978 June 7 (Video 26)
    - Politics and nutrition (boy who called "wolf"), 1978 June 13 (Video 27)
    - Legacy of the pioneers, 1978 July 24 (Video 28)
    - Department of Housing and Urban Development, 1978 August 10 (Video 29)
    - Truth in menus, 1978 August 13 (Video 30)
    - Don Gale audition tape, 1978 August 15 (Video 31)
    - People's energy bill, 1978 August 16 (Video 32)
    - Philo Farnsworth's birthday, 1978 August 19 (Video 33)
    - Mosquito opinion survey, 1978 August 22 (Video 34)
    - Unification of city and county governments, 1978 August 24 (Video 35)
    - Little League football, 1978 August 28 (Video 36)
    - County communication system (sheriff/police), 1978 August 29 (Video 37)
    - A dime's worth of optimism, 1978 August 31 (Video 38)
    - EPA blackmail, 1978 August 25 (Video 39)
    - Let's put an end to arson, 1978 September 1 (Video 40)
    - Colorado squawfish, 1978 September 13 (Video 41)
    - Physical fitness boom, 1978 September 18 (Video 42)
  - KSL editorials, 1978 September-1978 October; DVD (Disc 2)
    - Let's put an end to arson, 1978 September 1 (Video 1)
    - Government spending and personal income, 1978 September 2 (Video 2)
    - Turning good citizens to bad, 1978 September 3 (Video 3)
    - Smoke detectors, 1978 September 4 (Video 4)
    - Traffic fatalities, 1978 September 5 (Video 5)
    - Health insurance plan, 1978 September 6 (Video 6)
    - Gas tank vapor vacuum, 1978 September 7 (Video 7)
    - Mass transportation and metro, 1978 September 8 (Video 8)
    - Limiting government spending, 1978 September 9 (Video 9)
    - Problems of the super rich, 1978 September 10 (Video 10)
    - Schools, b-plus; parents, d, 1978 September 11 (Video 11)
    - Treatment of juvenile offenders, 1978 September 12 (Video 12)
    - The Colorado squawfish, 1978 September 13 (Video 13)
    - Cooperation in law enforcement, 1978 September 14 (Video 14)
    - Distribution of the tax burden, 1978 September 15 (Video 15)
    - Trouble at the airport, 1978 September 16 (Video 16)
    - Another viewpoint (high expectations), 1978 September 17 (Video 17)
    - Physical fitness boom, 1978 September 18 (Video 18)
    - Health care cost containment, 1978 September 19 (Video 19)
    - Threats by the E.P.A., 1978 September 20 (Video 20)
    - Controlling computerized x-rays, 1978 September 21 (Video 21)
    - Freedom is compromise, 1978 September 22 (Video 22)
    - The Camp David summit, 1978 September 23 (Video 23)
    - Jogging and joint injury, 1978 September 24 (Video 24)
    - The mill levies are set, 1978 September 25 (Video 25)
    - Conduct the public's business in public, 1978 September 26 (Video 26)
    - Treatment of juvenile offenders, 1978 September 27 (Video 27)
    - Wild, wild wilderness, 1978 September 28 (Video 28)
    - New Senate office building, 1978 September 29 (Video 29)
    - Priorities in spending, 1978 September 30 (Video 30)
    - The changing lifestyle (not recorded for archive), 1978 October 1 (Video 31)
    - Home for hte Utah State Fair, 1978 October 2 (Video 32)
    - Problems with property tax, 1978 October 3 (Video 33)
    - Mice in the mansion, 1978 October 4 (Video 34)
    - Closing Fort Douglas, 1978 October 5 (Video 35)
    - Utah's welfare fund, 1978 October 6 (Video 36)
    - Free enterprise on campus, 1978 October 7 (Video 37)
    - Postal Service ZIP codes, 1978 October 8 (Video 38)
    - Property tax overcharge, 1978 October 9 (Video 39)
    - Another point of view (Alaska), 1978 October 10 (Video 40)
    - Loose gravel on the highways, 1978 October 11 (Video 41)
    - Judicial war on the press, 1978 October 12 (Video 42)
    - Another point of view (consolidation), 1978 October 13 (Video 43)
    - The F.D.A. and Nitrites, 1978 October 14 (Video 44)
    - Graft and fraud at G.S.A., 1978 October 15 (Video 45)
    - Freedom and tolerance, 1978 October 16 (Video 46)
    - Teachers's strike, 1978 October 17 (Video 47)
    - Little's law of tax tinkering, 1978 October 18 (Video 48)
    - Veto of central utah project funds, 1978 October 19 (Video 49)
    - The magazine hustlers, 1978 October 20 (Video 50)
    - Taxi cabs in Salt Lake, 1978 October 21 (Video 51)
    - Zoning and property rights, 1978 October 22 (Video 52)
    - United Nations week, 1978 October 23 (Video 53)
    - Destroy the weteye bombs, 1978 October 24 (Video 54)
    - Competency testing for graduates, 1978 October 25 (Video 55)
    - Air quality standards, 1978 October 26 (Video 56)
    - The power of the few, 1978 October 27 (Video 57)
    - Another point of view (truth in menus), 1978 October 28 (Video 58)
    - Knowledge of History, 1978 October 29 (Video 59)
    - Trade-in time, 1978 October 30 (Video 60)
    - Letters from Listeners, 1978 October 31 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1978 November-1978 December; DVD (Disc 3)
    - Truth in menus (Larry Guba rebuttal) (not recorded for archive), 1978 November 1 (Video 1)
    - The important unification vote (not recorded for archive), 1978 November 2 (Video 2)
    - Another point of view (Mayor Thompson), 1978 November 3 (Video 3)
    - Solar energy subsidy, 1978 November 4 (Video 4)
    - The John Singer case, 1978 November 5 (Video 5)
    - School board elections, 1978 November 6 (Video 6)
    - The president and inflation, 1978 November 7 (Video 7)
    - Autumn canvas, 1978 November 8 (Video 8)
    - Teachers in the legislature, 1978 November 9 (Video 9)
    - Scrap the air bags, 1978 November 10 (Video 10)
    - Printing Control Act, 1978 November 11 (Video 11)
    - Tax burden study, 1978 November 12 (Video 12)
    - Shortages of nurses, 1978 November 13 (Video 13)
    - The comedian's friend, 1978 November 14 (Video 14)
    - Utah's hunter education program, 1978 November 15 (Video 15)
    - A tax saving that isn't, 1978 November 16 (Video 16)
    - Another point of view, 1978 November 17 (Video 17)
    - The 55 MPH fuel saver, 1978 November 18 (Video 18)
    - Taxes and individual responsibility, 1978 November 19 (Video 19)
    - Zoning for the people, 1978 November 20 (Video 20)
    - Wasatch Boulevard bottleneck, 1978 November 21 (Video 21)
    - Who's running state government?, 1978 November 22 (Video 22)
    - Thanksgiving, 1978 November 23 (Video 23)
    - The psychology of inflation, 1978 November 24 (Video 24)
    - What happened to creativity, 1978 November 25 (Video 25)
    - Represenation from the District of Columbia, 1978 November 26 (Video 26)
    - Threat to the free press, 1978 November 27 (Video 27)
    - Unification post-mortem, 1978 November 28 (Video 28)
    - Campaign spending limits, 1978 November 29 (Video 29)
    - The times of London, 1978 November 30 (Video 30)
    - Personal money management, 1978 December 1 (Video 31)
    - Utah's no fault insurance law, 1978 December 2 (Video 32)
    - Savings and inflation, 1978 December 3 (Video 33)
    - The equal rights amendment, 1978 December 4 (Video 34)
    - State employee merit system, 1978 December 5 (Video 35)
    - Let's clear the air at U.T.A., 1978 December 6 (Video 36)
    - Too many doctors, 1978 December 7 (Video 37)
    - The cost/benefits ratio of regulation, 1978 December 8 (Video 38)
    - Productivity level, 1978 December 9 (Video 39)
    - Over-reaction to tragedy, 1978 December 10 (Video 40)
    - Energy-cost labels ofr appliances, 1978 December 11 (Video 41)
    - The long road back, 1978 December 12 (Video 42)
    - Sugar plant shutdown, 1978 December 13 (Video 43)
    - Unions, sandwiches, and soda pop, 1978 December 14 (Video 44)
    - Quarters for Christmas, 1978 December 15 (Video 45)
    - Pension plan power, 1978 December 16 (Video 46)
    - Anniversary of flight, 1978 December 17 (Video 47)
    - Payment of property taxes, 1978 December 18 (Video 48)
    - County government cost increases, 1978 December 19 (Video 49)
    - Another point of view (Lowell Bennion), 1978 December 20 (Video 50)
    - Shortage of technical workers, 1978 December 21 (Video 51)
    - Quick thinking on oil spill, 1978 December 22 (Video 52)
    - Freedom and tolerance, 1978 December 23 (Video 53)
    - Christmas Eve, 1978 December 24 (Video 54)
    - Christmas Day, 1978 December 25 (Video 55)
    - Year-end roundup (i), 1978 December 26 (Video 56)
    - Year-end roundup (ii), 1978 December 27 (Video 57)
    - Year-end roundup (iii), 1978 December 28 (Video 58)
    - Year-end roundup (iv), 1978 December 29 (Video 59)
    - Year-end roundup (v), 1978 December 30 (Video 60)
    - New Year's Eve, 1978 December 31 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1979 January-1979 February; DVD (Disc 4)
    - New Year's Day, 1979 January 1 (Video 1)
    - Too many bowl game, 1979 January 2 (Video 2)
    - Another point of view (Roger Black), 1979 January 3 (Video 3)
    - House tax limitation committee, 1979 January 4 (Video 4)
    - Hill Air Force Base open house (not recorded for archive), 1979 January 5 (Video 5)
    - Minimum wage and unemployment, 1979 January 6 (Video 6)
    - Music and the savage beast, 1979 January 7 (Video 7)
    - Utah State Legislature, 1979 January 8 (Video 8)
    - Public employee wage demands, 1979 January 9 (Video 9)
    - Another point of view (Rep. Sam Taylor), 1979 January 10 (Video 10)
    - Senator Frank Church, 1979 January 11 (Video 11)
    - Recognition of China, 1979 January 12 (Video 12)
    - Walk for good health, 1979 January 13 (Video 13)
    - Closing the terrace, 1979 January 14 (Video 14)
    - The great wall of wilderness, 1979 January 15 (Video 15)
    - Intoxication Treatment Act, 1979 January 16 (Video 16)
    - Observe the speed limit, 1979 January 17 (Video 17)
    - Foreign investment in America, 1979 January 18 (Video 18)
    - The Governor's budget, 1979 January 19 (Video 19)
    - Commissioner Salter on the air, 1979 January 20 (Video 20)
    - Downzoning on the avenues, 1979 January 21 (Video 21)
    - Judicial salaries, 1979 January 22 (Video 22)
    - The closing of Auerbach's, 1978 November 23 (Video 23)
    - Rescue and risk, 1979 January 24 (Video 24)
    - Local option sales tax, 1979 January 25 (Video 25)
    - The many tragedies of John Singer, 1979 January 26 (Video 26)
    - Inflation and Political Action, 1979 January 27 (Video 27)
    - Freedom and regulation, 1979 January 28 (Video 28)
    - Questions for the Board of Inquiry, 1979 January 29 (Video 29)
    - Another point of view (Jed Kee), 1979 January 30 (Video 30)
    - School population growth, 1979 January 31 (Video 31)
    - Another point of view (Barry Wirth), 1979 February 1 (Video 32)
    - Feedback: government employee wage demands, 1979 February 2 (Video 33)
    - The Budget of H.E.W., 1979 February 3 (Video 34)
    - Utah's growing reputation, 1979 February 4 (Video 35)
    - Another point of view (Dick Carter), 1979 February 5 (Video 36)
    - Gerrymandering in Emigration Canyon, 1979 February 6 (Video 37)
    - Reserve Accounts on Mortgages, 1979 February 7 (Video 38)
    - Primary CHildren's Medical Center Radiothon, 1979 February 8 (Video 39)
    - Support for victims, 1979 February 9 (Video 40)
    - The promise of gasohol, 1979 February 10 (Video 41)
    - The changing scene, 1979 February 11 (Video 42)
    - Drinking driver intervention act, 1979 February 12 (Video 43)
    - The role of the property tax, 1979 February 13 (Video 44)
    - The young crime stoppers, 1979 February 14 (Video 45)
    - The Utah megalopolis, 1979 February 15 (Video 46)
    - City commission in trouble, 1979 February 16 (Video 47)
    - Witnesses of execution, 1979 February 17 (Video 48)
    - Letter to legislators, 1979 February 18 (Video 49)
    - Another point of view (Michael Holt), 1979 February 19 (Video 50)
    - Career education work, 1979 February 20 (Video 51)
    - Where do we go from here?, 1979 February 21 (Video 52)
    - Public service commission replacement, 1979 February 22 (Video 53)
    - Utah Transit Authority in trouble, 1979 February 23 (Video 54)
    - Welfare state in trouble, 1979 February 24 (Video 55)
    - The court and restaurant inspection, 1979 February 25 (Video 56)
    - Changes at the executive level, 1979 February 26 (Video 57)
    - Control of school expenditures, 1979 February 27 (Video 58)
    - Another point of view (Gloria Symes), 1979 February 28 (Video 59)
  - KSL editorials, 1979 March-1979 April; DVD (Disc 5)
    - Thanks to the press, 1979 March 1 (Video 1)
    - Feedback (great wall of wilderness), 1979 March 2 (Video 2)
    - Fishing and free enterprise, 1979 March 3 (Video 3)
    - Morality, education, and the law, 1979 March 4 (Video 4)
    - The value of private schools, 1979 March 5 (Video 5)
    - Salt on the highways, 1979 March 6 (Video 6)
    - Book burning and mind control, 1979 March 7 (Video 7)
    - Television's great promise, 1979 March 8 (Video 8)
    - Action agency under fire, 1979 March 9 (Video 9)
    - Cut congressional staffs, 1979 March 10 (Video 10)
    - Hooray for heroes, 1979 March 11 (Video 11)
    - Traffic light control, 1979 March 12 (Video 12)
    - Another point of view (Dr. Harry Gibbons), 1979 March 13 (Video 13)
    - Albert Einstein's birthday, 1979 March 14 (Video 14)
    - Another point view (Daryl McCarty), 1979 March 15 (Video 15)
    - The constitutional convention issue, 1979 March 16 (Video 16)
    - One-way streets in Salt Lake City, 1979 March 17 (Video 17)
    - Compact failure threatens C.U.P., 1979 March 18 (Video 18)
    - Agriculture day, 1979 March 19 (Video 19)
    - Fright treatment for juvenile offenders, 1979 March 20 (Video 20)
    - The vernal equinox, 1979 March 21 (Video 21)
    - Tax legislation is a failure, 1979 March 22 (Video 22)
    - Welcome to N.C.A.A. champs, 1979 March 23 (Video 23)
    - Traffic flow and fuel consumption, 1979 March 24 (Video 24)
    - The marvels of Voyager, 1979 March 25 (Video 25)
    - The banks and the tax increase, 1979 March 26 (Video 26)
    - Another point of view (Dr. Clark Puffer), 1979 March 27 (Video 27)
    - Children and television ads, 1979 March 28 (Video 28)
    - How Utahns view regulation, 1979 March 29 (Video 29)
    - Holes in the tax bill, 1979 March 30 (Video 30)
    - Decline of the consumer movement, 1979 March 31 (Video 31)
    - Rights and responsiblities, 1979 April 1 (Video 32)
    - Recertification of teachers, 1979 April 2 (Video 33)
    - Another point of view (Jess Agraz), 1979 April 3 (Video 34)
    - Alphabet Soup, 1979 April 4 (Video 35)
    - Ethics and congress, 1979 April 5 (Video 36)
    - Pressure on Planning and Zoning Commission, 1979 April 6 (Video 37)
    - To tax or not to tax, 1979 April 7 (Video 38)
    - F.D.A. weight proposal, 1979 April 8 (Video 39)
    - Profits and prices, 1979 April 9 (Video 40)
    - Conidtions at Utah State Prison, 1979 April 10 (Video 41)
    - Council-mayor city government, 1979 April 11 (Video 42)
    - Danger at three mile island, 1979 April 12 (Video 43)
    - The high cost of transportation, 1979 April 13 (Video 44)
    - Sears, Roebuck class-action suit, 1979 April 14 (Video 45)
    - The celebration season, 1979 April 15 (Video 46)
    - Thanks to the maestro, 1979 April 16 (Video 47)
    - The president and windfall profits, 1979 April 17 (Video 48)
    - To the F.D.A. and vitamins, 1979 April 18 (Video 49)
    - Trade-offs for nuclear power, 1979 April 19 (Video 50)
    - Minimize the energy crisis, 1979 April 20 (Video 51)
    - Business as a tax collector, 1979 April 21 (Video 52)
    - Rumors and reality, 1979 April 22 (Video 53)
    - The high cost of beef, 1979 April 23 (Video 54)
    - Another point of view (Tom Breitling), 1979 April 24 (Video 55)
    - Cameras in the courtroom, 1979 April 25 (Video 56)
    - Arbor Day, 1979 April 26 (Video 57)
    - Hidden raises for congress, 1979 April 27 (Video 58)
    - Someone is listening, 1979 April 28 (Video 59)
    - Erosion of the first ammendment, 1979 April 29 (Video 60)
    - Big oil and free enterprise, 1979 April 30 (Video 61)
  - KSL editorials, 1979 May-1979 June; DVD (Disc 6)
    - Another point of view (David Duncan), 1979 May 1 (Video 1)
    - Vote "yes" on mayor-council, 1979 May 2 (Video 2)
    - Feedback, 1979 May 3 (Video 3)
    - When no one says "hello", 1979 May 4 (Video 4)
    - Corporate profits in perspective, 1979 May 5 (Video 5)
    - Barriers to the handicapped, 1979 May 6 (Video 6)
    - Your chance to help, 1979 May 7 (Video 7)
    - Propaganda magazine for kids, 1979 May 8 (Video 8)
    - Watch the news... carefully, 1979 May 9 (Video 9)
    - The failing railroads, 1979 May 10 (Video 10)
    - Talk about fringe benefits!, 1979 May 11 (Video 11)
    - Prices, wages, and guidelines, 1979 May 12 (Video 12)
    - Gasoline shortages in Utah, 1979 May 13 (Video 13)
    - The election of Mrs. Thatcher, 1979 May 14 (Video 14)
    - Tyranny by the few, 1979 May 15 (Video 15)
    - Nevada land plans, 1979 May 16 (Video 16)
    - Another point of view (not recorded for archive), 1979 May 17 (Video 17)
    - Salt Lake Art Center opens, 1979 May 18 (Video 18)
    - Let's solve the oil problem, 1979 May 19 (Video 19)
    - Courtesy on the road, 1979 May 20 (Video 20)
    - Sacrifice is for everyone, 1979 May 21 (Video 21)
    - Honesty deserves a little courtesy, 1979 May 22 (Video 22)
    - Thanks to our teenage workers, 1979 May 23 (Video 23)
    - On the sensitivity of educators, 1979 May 24 (Video 24)
    - How to price gasoline, 1979 May 25 (Video 25)
    - The commuter bus goes private, 1979 May 26 (Video 26)
    - Message to graduates, 1979 May 27 (Video 27)
    - Let 'em eat cake, 1979 May 28 (Video 28)
    - Job-hunting for graduates, 1979 May 29 (Video 29)
    - Anti-knock octane labels, 1979 May 30 (Video 30)
    - Sugarhouse Park, 1979 May 31 (Video 31)
    - A generation of television, 1979 June 1 (Video 32)
    - Hamburgers are an endangered species, 1979 June 2 (Video 33)
    - The four-day work week, 1979 June 3 (Video 34)
    - Call for mayoral candidates, 1979 June 4 (Video 35)
    - Help for home mortgages, 1979 June 5 (Video 36)
    - To the bride and groom, 1979 June 6 (Video 37)
    - Nuts to self-sufficiency, 1979 June 7 (Video 38)
    - It's time to rock the boat, 1979 June 8 (Video 39)
    - Hold the salt ii, 1979 June 9 (Video 40)
    - The quality of justice, 1979 June 10 (Video 41)